http://www.tse.com/privacy-policy

TMX POV
TMX (X):
Search
Search results will open in a new window on money.tmx.com.
HOME
TMX Group
TMX Group
TMX operates global markets, and builds digital communities and analytic solutions that facilitate the funding, growth and success of businesses, traders and investors.
TMX Market Centre
Facility Rentals
Media Services
Market Open Ceremony
TMX Group Companies
Toronto Stock Exchange
TSX Venture Exchange
TSX Trust
Investor Relations
TMX operates global markets, and builds digital communities and analytic solutions that facilitate the funding, growth and success of businesses, traders and investors.
Share Information
Quarterly and Annual Reports
Dividends
Analyst Coverage
Debt Information
Corporate Information
Board of Directors
Senior Management
Careers
TMX operates global markets, and builds digital communities and analytic solutions that facilitate the funding, growth and success of businesses, traders and investors.
Career Opportunities
If you are interested in joining our team, we invite you to apply for a position at TMX Group.
Life @ TMX
Work @ TMX
Campus Recruitment
Employee Experience
The TMX team is hard at work, driven to succeed, and focused on serving our customers and the marketplace as a whole.
Training & Development
Compensation & Benefits
Corporate Citizenship
Newsroom
Newsroom
Home to our recent corporate announcements, speeches and market notices.
Press Releases
Speeches
TSX & TSXV Market Notices
Market Opens
New Company Listings
Reviews and Suspensions
Media Contacts
TMX POV
TMX POV
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out the information gathering and dissemination practices of TMX Group Limited ("TMX Group") and its affiliates and subsidiaries (collectively, the "TMX" or "we") in the use of TMX's websites (collectively, "the Websites"). By using the Websites, you are consenting to this privacy policy and the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information by TMX as outlined in this privacy policy. If this privacy policy is not acceptable to you, please do not submit any of your personal information.
We may update this privacy policy from time to time and you are responsible for periodically reviewing the most current version of this privacy policy on the Websites. Your continued use of the Websites or submission of information will be deemed your conclusive acceptance of the updated privacy policy.
In this Privacy Policy, the phrase "Service Providers" includes, but is not limited to, any licensors, suppliers, information providers or other third parties that provide or administer, from time to time, any data, information, content, application, tool or service to TMX.
Collecting, Using and Disclosing Information
This privacy policy describes our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of the personal information that we (or our Service Providers on our behalf) collect about you on the Websites such as your name, address, phone number, fax number, e-mail address or payment information. We may collect this information when you subscribe to, or sign your company up for, certain services, tools or features that we provide, when you register for seminars or other programs that we offer, when you fill out forms made available through the Websites, when you enter a promotion or contest, when you complete a survey, when you e-mail us with general inquiries or with your comments or suggestions, when you make a purchase or otherwise in connection with your use of the Websites. We will limit the personal information we collect to what we need for the purposes for which it was collected, and will use such personal information for such purposes. We may also use personal information we collect to provide you with information on products, services and events that we or third parties offer that we believe may be of interest to you. If we wish to use your personal information for any other purpose, we will obtain your consent before using the information.
Storing of Information and Restricting Access
We may store your personal information (in encrypted form where we believe it to be highly sensitive) in electronic databases or e-mail boxes hosted by us or our Service Providers, for periods of time and with safeguards that we believe are reasonable depending on the nature and sensitivity of the information. Access to the information is restricted in accordance with our security protocols.
Certain features on the Websites are password-protected to prevent unauthorized access. You are responsible for the confidentiality and use of such passwords.
Due to the nature of Internet communications and evolving technologies, TMX cannot provide assurance that the personal information we collect will remain free from loss, interception, misuse or alteration by third parties and TMX and its Service Providers shall have no liability for any loss, interception, misuse or alteration.
Automatic Collection of Information
In some cases, we may collect information about you that may or may not be personally-identifiable. Examples of this type of information include your Internet protocol (IP) address, the type of Internet browser you are using, the type of computer operating system you are using, and the advertisement or domain name of the website from which you linked to the Websites. The collection, use, disclosure and storage of such information will be in accordance with this privacy policy, including for the purpose of optimizing Website user experience.
Cookies
Some pages on the Websites use a technology called "cookies". A cookie is a token that a server gives to your browser when you access a website. Cookies are capable of storing many types of data. Cookies may be placed by TMX or a third party. Cookies help provide additional functionality to the Websites or help provide and analyze Website traffic and usage information. For instance, our server may set a cookie that keeps you from having to enter a password more than once during a visit to one of the Websites. In all cases in which cookies are used, we will not collect personally-identifiable information except with your permission. With most Internet browsers, you can erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Please refer to your browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions.
Releasing Information
We may provide your personal information to other persons but only if:
we have your consent;
we provide the information to Service Providers who assist us in serving you and who have agreed to appropriate contractual provisions regarding the protection of personal information in accordance with applicable law; or
we are required to do so by law, regulation or court order.
Your personal information may be transferred (or otherwise made available) to our affiliates and other third parties who provide services on our behalf. For example, we use Service Providers to assist us process, store and secure data. This may include sending email or other communications using their online services. Our Service Providers are given the information they need to perform their designated functions, and are not authorized to use or disclose personal information for their own purposes. Your personal information may be maintained and processed by us, our affiliates and other third party Service Providers in other jurisdictions. In the event personal information is transferred to another jurisdiction, it will be subject to the laws of that jurisdiction and may be disclosed to or accessed by the courts, law enforcement and governmental authorities in accordance with those laws.
Respecting and Responding to Your Privacy Concerns
You have the option to refuse or withdraw consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information, and we will respect your choices. If you wish to exercise this option or if you have any questions or enquiries with respect to our privacy policies or procedures, please send a written request to: Chief Privacy Officer, TMX Group, 100 Adelaide St. West, Toronto, ON, M5H 1S3. We will investigate and respond to your concerns about any aspect of our handling of your information.
BY USING THE WEBSITES, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY, UNDERSTAND IT AND AGREE TO ALL OF THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY.
Updated May 20, 2016
Top
Capital Formation
Toronto Stock Exchange
TSX Venture Exchange
TSX Trust
Markets
Montréal Exchange
YouTube
TMX Group Limited and its affiliates do not endorse or recommend any securities issued by any companies identified on, or linked through, this site. Please seek professional advice to evaluate specific securities or other content on this site. All content (including any links to third party sites) is provided for informational purposes only (and not for trading purposes), and is not intended to provide legal, accounting, tax, investment, financial or other advice and should not be relied upon for such advice. The views, opinions and advice of any third party reflect those of the individual authors and are not endorsed by TMX Group Limited or its affiliates. TMX Group Limited and its affiliates have not prepared, reviewed or updated the content of third parties on this site or the content of any third party sites, and assume no responsibility for such information.
Copyright © 2020 TSX Inc. All rights reserved.
